good afternoon I'm my name is Alan
下午好，我叫艾伦
Bateman I'm giving a talk called
贝特曼，我正在讲一个电话
prepared for JDK 9 if you're looking in
如果您正在寻找JDK 9的准备
the content cut and catalog you may have
您可能拥有的内容剪切和目录
seen it it's actually Alex Buckley
看到它实际上是亚历克斯·巴克利
supposed to be speaking that was just a
应该说那只是一个
bit of the mix-up with the names so one
有点混乱的名字
my left here is actually Alex Buckley
我在这里实际上是亚历克斯·巴克利（Alex Buckley）
and beyond him is mark Reinhold they may
而在他身旁的是马克·莱因霍尔德，他们可能
help with some questions at the end so
最后帮助一些问题，这样
before we get into this presentation I
在我们进入这个演讲之前，我
just want to say that this is not a
只想说这不是一个
presentation about all the cool features
所有酷功能的介绍
and the big long list of jets that Mark
还有马克的一长串喷气机
showed in the keynote this is not about
在主题演讲中显示这不是关于
all the new things in JDK 9 this is
JDK 9中的所有新功能是
instead a talk that's focused on the
而是专注于
implications of the changes in JDK 9
JDK 9中更改的含义
particularly around the the strong
特别是在强者周围
capsulation of the the JDK internal
JDK内部封装
api's which a lot of applications and
api的应用程序很多，
libraries have been making use of over
图书馆已经在利用
the years there are a couple of small
这些年有几个小
features in JDK 9 that I want that help
我需要该功能的JDK 9中的功能
with the migration and help with
与迁移和帮助
interrupts between JDK 8 and 9 that it
JDK 8和9之间的中断
will spend a few minutes on towards the
将花几分钟的时间
end of the presentation but for the most
演讲结束但大部分
part this is about the implications of
这部分是关于
JDK 9 so before I start I guess I would
JDK 9所以在我开始之前我想我会
be interested to have some idea from
有兴趣从
this audience as to how many people in
观众中有多少人
this audience are tracking the features
该受众群体正在跟踪功能
and the changes that are going into JDK
以及进入JDK的更改
9 okay so there's a couple people and
9好的，所以有几个人
I'm curious first your hands as to those
首先，我对你的手感到好奇
that have actually downloaded the JDK 9
实际上已经下载了JDK 9
early access bills to try things out
抢先体验账单来尝试一下
similar number of hands okay here's the
类似的手数好吧，这是
strange question who has concerns that
一个奇怪的问题，谁担心
there are changes in JDK 9 that might
JDK 9中可能会有更改
break their existing code or the
破坏他们现有的代码或
existing applications a couple of hands
现有应用程序
okay that's that's that that's fine that
好的那就是那很好
this is what this presentation is about
这就是这个演讲的目的
one thing before I get into this is I
在我进入这个之前的一件事是我
should explain is JDK 9 is still a
应该说明的是JDK 9仍然是
development it's not going to ship until
开发，直到发布
or plan to be shipped in 2017 there's a
或计划在2017年发货
lot of things that are still changing in
许多仍在变化的事物
it there's nothing that is final yet so
没有什么是最终的，所以
when I'm talking about and some of the
当我谈论和一些
changes
变化
maybe that'll be where it is when it
也许那会是当它在哪里
finally ships maybe there'll be some
最终出货，也许会有一些
differences so just bear in mind that
差异，因此请记住
it's not final yet first thing just to
这不是最终的，但第一件事只是
get into this present into this
进入这个礼物
presentation just says it's the first of
演示文稿只是说这是第一个
five presentations that Alex and I are
我和亚历克斯的五个演讲
doing at JavaOne this year and the rest
今年在JavaOne上做，其余的
of our talks after this one are very
在这之后我们的谈话非常
much focused on the modularity and the
非常关注模块化和
all the features around around modules
模块周围的所有功能
in the JDK we're repeating four of these
在JDK中，我们重复其中的四个
and I'll have a slide at the end with
最后我将有一张幻灯片
the the times and locations of those so
这些人的时间和地点
you can see what we're talking about on
您可以看到我们在谈论什么
when it's on I want to go through a
当它打开时，我想经历一个
couple of background slides before we
我们之前的几张背景幻灯片
get into the metres presentation and so
进入电表演示等等
first is just some of the background for
首先只是一些背景
what the goals for JDK 9 and project
JDK 9和项目的目标是什么
jigsaw are so at a high level what what
拼图如此高层次是什么
we're trying to do is is make the Java
我们试图做的是使Java
platform and Java see a lot more
平台和Java会看到更多
flexible and scalable and allows get to
灵活且可扩展，并允许
the point where there's a lot more
还有更多的地方
reliable and compact deployments so
可靠而紧凑的部署，因此
deploying runtimes in the cloud or on
在云中或之上部署运行时
embedded systems we're trying to get to
我们试图达到的嵌入式系统
the point where we have a more more more
我们拥有更多的点
secure and maintainable platform when we
安全和可维护的平台，当我们
talk about security we're talking about
谈论我们正在谈论的安全性
encapsulating this very much the
封装了很多
security sensitive and internal api's
安全敏感和内部api
and within modules and for
以及模块内和
maintainability having these strong
具有这些强大的可维护性
capsulation and encapsulating the
封装和封装
eternal api's will make things a lot
永恒的api会让事情变得很多
more maintainable for the JDK it'll also
对于JDK更具可维护性
make it much more maintainable for and
使它更易于维护
for libraries and for those using
对于图书馆和使用
libraries because a lot of libraries and
库，因为很多库和
applications are making use of internal
应用程序正在使用内部
API api's in other libraries maybe
其他库中的API api可能
knowingly maybe unknowingly
可能是在不知不觉中
so having modules will get us to the
因此拥有模块将使我们进入
point where things are a lot more
指出更多的地方
maintainable we want to make it easy to
可维护的，我们想使其易于
construct maintain deploy and upgrade
构建维护部署和升级
large applications and that's both Java
大型应用程序，而且都是Java
C applications and eventually in the
C应用程序，最终在
future Java EE applications we and
我们和未来的Java EE应用程序
importantly we want to move towards
重要的是我们要朝着
improving
改善
the situation with what's called Jar Jar
所谓的Jar Jar情况
Jar hell and which we have with the
地狱，我们与
classpath today so we'll go a long way
今天的classpath，所以我们会走很长一段路
to improving the situation and with with
改善情况，并与
modules in JDK 9
JDK 9中的模块
and finally there's what we're doing at
最后是我们在做的
modules we'll actually go and enable a
我们将实际使用的模块并启用
lot more performance improvements in the
在性能上有很多改进
future so I want to start by going into
未来，所以我想从开始
some of the categories of api's that you
您的一些api类别
have and with the Java platform we all
拥有并且拥有Java平台
know the Java dot star and Java X dot
知道Java点星号和Java X点
star api's so we use java.lang object or
星型api，因此我们使用java.lang对象或
javax.swing jpanel or something like
javax.swing jpanel或类似的东西
that these are standard Java SE api's
这些是标准的Java SE api
they're they're tied to the java
他们是他们绑在java上
community process they get defined there
他们在那里定义的社区过程
they're supported and documented api's
他们得到支持并记录了api
we all understand those there's a bunch
我们都知道那里有一堆
of other api's that are always a little
其他的api总是有点
bit confusing that we call them jdk
有点令人困惑，我们称它们为jdk
specific api's these api's are typically
特定的api这些api通常是
in the at least historically have been
在至少历史上
in the comm sun namespace if you go to
如果您转到comm sun命名空间中
the the the documentation pages you will
您将在文档页面中找到
actually see a number of documented
实际看到一些记录
Khamsin api's for security for
Khamsin API的安全性
management and for a few other areas and
管理和其他一些领域
in recent jdk releases these jdk
在最近的JDK发布中，这些JDK
specific api's have been in the jdk dot
特定的api已经在jdk点中
something namespace because we have we
一些名称空间，因为我们拥有
have since we're no longer sun we have
因为我们不再是太阳
moved to and we're now an open JDK we've
移至，我们现在是一个开放的JDK
moved to defining these JDK specific API
着手定义这些JDK特定的API
is in the jdk namespace rahdert and Comm
在jdk命名空间rahdert和Comm中
some there's a whole bunch of other
有些还有一大堆其他
internal api's that are also in the comm
内部api也在通讯中
some namespace sometimes you'll see the
一些命名空间，有时您会看到
word internal in the package name and
包名称中的内部单词和
it's pretty clear that this is an
很明显，这是一个
internal package others are not as clear
内部包装其他不清楚
so there's always been confusion around
所以周围总是有混乱
these then there is the Sun dot star
这些就是太阳点星
namespace most people will know that if
命名空间，大多数人会知道，如果
they see a Sun dot star API that's
他们看到一个Sun点星API
probably JDK internal there has been Sun
可能是JDK内部出现了Sun
dot star api's all the way back to jdk
点星API一直回到jdk
1.0 so this is this this is a this is
1.0所以这是这是这是
captures a one of the pages from the
从中捕获页面之一
documentation from jdk 1.0 1.1
jdk 1.0 1.1中的文档
mark dug this out I think for Java one
我把这个标记挖出来对于Java
last year to to show the page where
去年显示页面在哪里
there was a warning about using Sun dot
有关于使用Sun dot的警告
star ap is the date on the bottom for
星号ap是底部底部的日期
those that can't read this I forgot to
那些看不懂的我忘了
bring binoculars it says 1996 at the
带双筒望远镜说1996年在
bottom of the page if I was to read out
如果我要读出页面底部
what it's what I've highlighted in red
这是我用红色突出显示的内容
it says that the Sun dots are packages
它说太阳点是包装
are not part of the supported Java
不属于受支持的Java
public interface a program that directly
公共接口程序直接
calls any API and Sun dot star packages
调用任何API和Sun dot star软件包
not guaranteed to work on all Java
不保证可以在所有Java上使用
compatible platforms so there has been a
兼容的平台，所以有一个
warning in the documentation for almost
文档中的警告几乎
20 years about not using Sun Deathstar
关于不使用Sun Deathstar的20年
api's in JDK 6
JDK 6中的api
this was actually enforced by the
这实际上是由
compiler so it actually emits a warning
编译器，因此它实际上会发出警告
if it attempts to compile code that's
如果它尝试编译的代码是
actually using any internal EAP is but
实际上使用任何内部EAP是
my guess is if I pull the audience's a
我的猜测是，如果我吸引观众
lot of people will not will not have
很多人不会有
seen this warning are they will ignore
看到这个警告，他们会忽略
the warning which we're all guilty of
我们都内of的警告
doing it's just a couple of things about
这只是关于几件事的事情
general compatibility policies before I
我之前的一般兼容性政策
get into some of the real slides is is
进入一些真正的幻灯片是
is that a high level if an application
如果一个应用程序是高水平的
is only using supported API and it works
仅使用受支持的API，并且有效
on a particular release then it should
在特定版本上，则应该
work on the next release and that's even
在下一个版本上工作，甚至
without complete compiling us if I have
如果我没有完整地编译我们
something on JDK so I've compiled it
JDK上的某些内容，所以我已经对其进行了编译
with JDK 7 it should run on JDK age
使用JDK 7时，它应该在JDK时代运行
without recompiling assuming it's using
无需重新编译（假设正在使用）
just the the supported api's this has
只是受支持的api的
been the compatibility story for the
一直是兼容性的故事
most part of 20 years and it means that
20年的大部分时间，这意味着
a lot of people can actually preserve
很多人实际上可以保存
their existing investment because they
他们现有的投资，因为他们
know or they have some confidence that
知道或他们有一定的信心
things will just work on the next the
事情只会在下一个
next release the JDK tries
JDK尝试的下一个发行版
what does not promise and is never
什么不会保证，永远不会
promised to and that it won't break
答应了，它不会中断
applications that are using internal
使用内部的应用程序
api's and incompatible changes in
api和不兼容的更改
supported api's tend to be confined to
支持的api往往仅限于
major releases sometimes with internal
主要发行版本有时带有内部
API is there is dirt there's breakage
API有污垢有破损
across other releases and what paper key
其他版本以及什么纸质钥匙
people try when they're working on the
人们在工作时尝试
JDK try to take into the into account
JDK尝试考虑到
the possibility to people are using
人们正在使用的可能性
those api's there is a policy that was
这些api的政策是
established a couple of couple releases
建立了几个发行版本
back to allow supported
返回以允许支持
guys be removed and this is this is not
伙计们被删除，这不是
something that's actually being used all
实际被所有使用的东西
that often and it's only something that
经常这样，只是
happens with significant advance notice
发生重大提前通知
for Java c9 we are proposing to remove a
对于Java c9，我们建议删除
small number of deprecated methods and
少数不推荐使用的方法和
we will see those later in the
我们会在后面看到
presentation just a couple of points
介绍只是几点
about managing incompatibilities and so
关于管理不兼容性等
managing compatibilities is all about
管理兼容性就是一切
judging risk and impact and a lot of the
判断风险和影响以及很多
time we're trying to use real data when
当我们试图使用真实数据的时候
trying to judge whether where something
试图判断是否有东西
is an incompatible change and what the
是不兼容的更改，
impact is there are many times where we
影响在很多时候
have run a done static analysis on
对完成了静态分析
thousands or tens of thousands of
成千上万
projects in in maven Center for example
例如在Maven Center中的项目
to get some idea about API usage so a
了解有关API使用情况的信息，因此
lot of data is often used when trying to
尝试时经常使用大量数据
figure out whether to make a change or
弄清楚是否要进行更改或
not when there are incompatible changes
不存在不兼容的更改时
we try to communicate early and often
我们尝试尽早交流
for some of the changes that we're
对于我们所做的一些改变
talking about for JDK 9 we've been
谈到JDK 9，我们一直在
actually talking about these now for
现在真的在谈论这些
almost 5 years and the things I'm
快五年了，我就是
talking about going to be talking about
谈论要谈论
that are that are proposed to be removed
建议删除的
are things that we had planned to remove
是我们计划删除的东西
a long long time ago we deprecated them
很久以前，我们已弃用它们
a long time ago in preparation for
很久以前
moving to modules and JDK 9 when we do
当我们做的时候转移到模块和JDK 9
incompatible changes is that we try to
不兼容的更改是我们尝试
make it easy to understand how tools and
易于理解工具和
code will be will be affected and a
代码将受到影响，并且
couple of people put up their hands to
几个人举起手来
say that they're testing out the early
说他们正在尽早测试
access bills that is really the time to
存取账单确实是时候
during the development of major release
在主要版本的开发过程中
to actually defined these
实际定义这些
incompatibility issues and early on
不兼容问题以及早期
there are times when we may make a
有时候我们可能会
change we may not realize what the
变化，我们可能不会意识到
impact is but well we get feedback and
影响是很好，但我们得到反馈，
we get grumbling from people that are
我们从那些
trying out the early access release to
试用早期访问版本
point things out that we may not have
指出我们可能没有的东西
actually spotted so having that kind of
实际上发现，所以有这种
feedback with the early access bills is
早期访问法案的反馈是
very very useful and and often as well
非常非常有用，而且经常
when making changes we have system
进行更改时，我们拥有系统
properties or we have other command-line
属性，或者我们还有其他命令行
options to retain
保留的选项
they are restore the behavior of old
他们正在恢复旧的行为
releases and if you look at them every
发行，如果您每看一次
major release of the JDK in the
JDK的主要版本
documentation there's all the system
文档，所有的系统
properties or other little knobs to be
属性或其他小旋钮
able to restore and retain all behavior
能够还原并保留所有行为
and finally we write lengthy migration
最后我们写了漫长的迁移
and release notes I don't know how many
和发行说明，我不知道有多少
people actually read them but there's an
人们实际上读了它们，但是有一个
every single major release has an
每个主要版本都有一个
exhaustive list of release notes that
发行说明的详尽清单
document all the compatibility issues
记录所有兼容性问题
that we are aware of okay at a high
我们知道高就可以
level these are some of the incompatible
这些是一些不兼容的
changes in JDK 9 and the important one
JDK 9中的重要变化
that I'm going to spend most of the time
我将大部分时间都花在
on is the first one which is
在第一个是
encapsulating most JDK internally api's
内部封装大多数JDK API
I want to talk a little bit about the
我想谈谈
binary structure of the JDK and a couple
JDK的二进制结构和几个
of things that have been removed and a
被移除的东西和
couple of other other changes and also
其他一些变化以及
the version change which turns out to be
版本更改原来是
quite a significant and issue so I'm
相当重要的问题，所以我
going to start with a data point which
从一个数据点开始
is which is based on on analysis that we
是基于我们的分析
did last year on the usages of JDK
去年做了关于JDK的用法
internal api's so this graph here is
内部API的，所以这里的图是
based on an analysis of about a hundred
根据对大约一百种的分析
different libraries and some popular
不同的图书馆和一些受欢迎的
open-source libraries and a couple of
开源库和几个
proprietary applications that we have
我们拥有的专有应用程序
that we are able to get our hands on so
这样我们就可以动手了
running some static analysis on this we
对此进行一些静态分析
get some idea of which of the JDK
了解哪个JDK
internal API s are actually being used
内部API实际上正在使用
the way this graph is is structured our
该图的结构方式
sorry showed is this is that the
抱歉显示这是因为
internal API are plotted on the x-axis
内部API绘制在x轴上
and the usage count is on the y-axis so
并且使用计数在y轴上，因此
looking from the left we can see that
从左边看，我们可以看到
based on this static analysis there's a
基于此静态分析，有一个
hundred and twenty five usages of some
一些的一百二十五用法
internal API and there's just over a
内部API，
hundred usages of oven of another
另一个烤箱的百次用法
internal API and we can see that there's
内部API，我们可以看到
a big long tail here this goes over on
长长的尾巴在这里继续
this corpus of of code that was that was
这是那段代码
examined there was over 700 different
检查了700多种
internal api's that were used
使用的内部api
so I'd I don't know if anyone would like
所以我不知道是否有人愿意
to guess what the most popular Sun dot
猜猜最流行的Sun点
star API that was used by this this code
此代码使用的star API
base that you are this this group of
就是说你就是这群人
libraries and applications that you
您所使用的库和应用程序
haven't seen does anyone want to give a
还没看到有人要给
gaze I hear someone said unsafe well
凝视着我听到有人说不安全
that's that's quite a good guess but for
那是一个很好的猜测，但对于
this for this group of libraries and
这对于这组图书馆和
applications it turns out to be some
应用程序，事实证明是一些
miss base64 encode er was the most
想念base64编码器是最多的
popular one use and Sun Sun miss gun
流行的一种用途和太阳孙小姐枪
safe wasn't wasn't too far behind if we
如果我们能够做到，安全就不会落后太远
were to go down to the third one it was
下降到第三个
actually some misc base64 decoder was
实际上有些杂项base64解码器是
the third most popular one use one thing
第三流行的一种用途
just to say about base64 is this is that
只是说说base64是这样的
we did finally after almost 20 years
经过近20年的努力，我们终于做到了
introduce a standard base64 API in Java
在Java中引入标准的base64 API
C ace finally so based based on this is
最后，基于此，Cace
there's a categorization of internal API
内部API有一个分类
is that was put together and I'll go
那是放在一起，我去
into and few minutes to talk a little
进去，聊了几分钟
bit about how this is documented in JEP
关于如何在JEP中进行记录
260 and what we can do when we look at
260，当我们看着
all of these usages of internal API is
内部API的所有这些用法是
we can essentially put them into two
我们基本上可以将它们分成两部分
buckets there's the non-critical api's
桶里有非关键的API
which is which is really the api's that
这真的是api的那个
are not really used by anything there's
没有被任何东西真正使用
no evidence that they're actually being
没有证据表明他们实际上是
used also in this Bacchus would be the
在此酒神中也将使用
internal API is that are really just
内部API实际上就是
being used by convenience someone
被某人方便使用
happened to find that there's a very
碰巧发现有一个非常
useful Sun that's our API so they make
有用的Sun是我们的API，因此他们可以
use of it there's no real reason to or
使用它没有真正的理由或
critical reason for it then there are
关键原因是
the critical API is some Muskaan safe
关键的API是Muskaan安全的
being the most obvious one it's not
最明显的不是
possible to to write your own Sun
可以写自己的太阳
Muskaan safe that is outside of the
Muskaan保险箱不在
platform and there's a small number of
平台，并且数量很少
other critical internal API is like this
其他关键内部API就是这样
so in JEP 260 sir JEP is is jdk
所以在JEP 260中，JEP是jdk
enhancement proposal is it's it's it's
增强建议是它是
it's how features and and other big
这就是功能和其他大功能
changes and significant changes in open
变化和重大变化
JDK are actually tracked we have JEP 260
实际跟踪到JDK，我们有JEP 260
than they're all numbered I should say
比我都应该说的都多
it proposes and this is what we have in
它提出了，这就是我们所拥有的
our current rate okay now in Bill
我们比尔现在的房价还可以
is encapsulate all non-critical internal
封装所有非关键内部
api's by default remember non-critical
api默认记住非关键
internal api's are those are no evidence
内部api是没有证据的
that they're being used or they're just
他们正在被使用或只是
being used for convenience we
为方便起见，我们
encapsulate all the critical internal
封装所有关键内部
API s which have supported replacements
支持替换的API
in in jdk age or Java SCH so if there's
在jdk时代或Java SCH中，如果有
not if there's really a supported API
如果确实有受支持的API，则不会
and there's no reason to use this in
而且没有理由在
turn this critical internal API then
然后打开这个关键的内部API
there's no reason why it should be
没有理由应该这样
available for widespread use in nine and
可在九个国家广泛使用
then the final one is do not encapsulate
那么最后一个是不封装
the critical internal API s like some
一些关键的内部API
Sun Muskaan safe and have the complete
Sun Muskaan安全且完整
list from G up to 60 in the next slide
在下一张幻灯片中从G到60的列表
instead what we want to do is is
相反，我们要做的是
deprecated them and and then plan to
弃用它们，然后计划
remove them once there is a supported
一旦有支持，将其删除
API available for them anything using
使用任何东西都可以使用的API
these using these api's will also have a
这些使用这些API的人也会有一个
workaround via the command line and
解决方法是通过命令行和
other means as you will see to be able
您将看到的其他方式
to still get at those api's when you
仍然可以在您使用这些api时
really need to so Jeff 260 as it stands
真的需要让Jeff 260保持现状
at the moment lists the following as
目前列出以下内容为
critical internal API s and Sun Muskaan
关键内部API和Sun Muskaan
safe which is critical to a lot of low
安全，这对很多低电量至关重要
level access and high performance
级别访问和高性能
libraries we have the the signal API
我们拥有信号API的库
which is related to just two signal
与两个信号有关
handling and reflection get call our
处理和反思请致电我们
class now that is widely used by logging
现在被日志记录广泛使用的类
frameworks there is a new stack walking
框架有一个新的栈走
API which was done as part of JEP 259 in
API是JEP 259中的一部分
for Java C 9 and and eventually we would
Java C 9，最终我们将
hope that the the logging frameworks and
希望日志记录框架和
other usages of this API would migrate
此API的其他用法将迁移
there then there's a Sun reflect
那里有阳光反射
reflection factory widely used by
反射工厂被广泛使用
serialization frameworks because it
序列化框架，因为它
provides some features that that you
提供您所需要的一些功能
need to be able to for example
需要能够例如
instantiate objects without running the
实例化对象而不运行
constructor things like that so just
诸如此类的构造函数
back to the data that we had in this a
回到我们在这个
couple of slides ago and so this is
几张幻灯片，所以这是
about a hundred different products and
大约一百种不同的产品
this actually puts labels sorry colors
这实际上使标签对不起颜色
on the internal api's that are actually
实际上是在内部api上
you
您
here and so that you can see how it
在这里，这样你就可以看到
relates to the categorization in the
涉及到
last two slides so when I look down
最后两张幻灯片，所以当我往下看时
through this and I realize the color
通过这个，我意识到颜色
it's hard to maybe differentiate this is
很难区分这是
those that are colored in orange if you
那些橙色的如果你
look at the second one down son Muskaan
看看第二个儿子穆斯卡恩（Muskaan）
safe that's the critical internal api's
安全是关键的内部api
purple which is quite a few of them from
紫色，其中很多
the Sun miss base64 encode and decode or
Sun缺少base64编码和解码，或者
near the top are the good examples
靠近顶部的是很好的例子
they are non-critical api's and there's
它们是非关键的api，并且
a supported API for them there was never
对他们来说，受支持的API从来没有
really any reason to use make use of the
确实有任何使用理由
JT case and turtle and version and
JT案例和乌龟以及版本和
anyway I'm Green are non critical and
无论如何，我是绿色的，并不重要，
non Sam but supported in nine that's a
非山姆，但有9个人支持
very small number of categories where
类别很少
when we looked at these internal API
当我们看这些内部API
usage realize oh these ones should
用法意识到这些应该
really have been supported api's so
确实得到了api的支持，所以
there's this these are w3c dumb XPath is
这些是w3c哑巴XPath是
that was a case where we weren't we
在这种情况下，我们不是
weren't doing the right thing in terms
在条款上没有做正确的事
of providing the aligning it with the
提供与
w3c api's and then read is no
w3c api的，然后读取为否
replacement sorry there's no date a lot
更换抱歉，没有很多约会
of these are just they're used for
这些只是它们用于
convenience how do you find these usages
方便如何找到这些用法
so just back to poll in the audience a
所以回到观众面前
minute is how many people here have
分钟是这里有多少人
heard of the J DEP stool okay maybe I
听说J DEP凳子好吧，也许我
see about maybe 10 10 hands here the J
看到这里大概有10 10手
depth stool is a tool that allows you to
深度凳子是一种工具，可让您
do a static analysis on your libraries
对您的库进行静态分析
and applications to see what ap eyes are
和应用程序，以了解什么是眼睛
actually being used what their
实际被用来
dependencies are that tool is in JDK H
依赖关系是该工具在JDK H中
we put that tool in as part of of
我们将该工具作为
preparing the platform to move to
准备迁移到的平台
modules and strong capsulation in the in
模块和强大的封装
the future it's really really useful
未来真的非常有用
with with an option called earth the
与一个称为地球的选择
option is named - jdk internal I would
选项名为-jdk内部，我会
have example in the next slide and that
在下一张幻灯片中有示例，
allows you to quickly see whether you
让您快速查看您是否
have any direct dependencies on JDK
对JDK有任何直接依赖
internal API s you can quickly run this
内部API，您可以快速运行
and point it at your jar files or your
并将其指向您的jar文件或
application and it will tell you if you
应用程序，它将告诉您是否
re making use of any JDK internally
在内部重新使用任何JDK
P is C Robert Shelton the in the
P是C罗伯特·谢尔顿在
audience there he's written a maven has
那里写的行家的观众
a plugin that actually uses J tips so
实际使用J技巧的插件
you can actually incorporate it into
您实际上可以将其合并到
your maven projects and so they can
您的Maven项目，因此他们可以
actually report I think and actually
实际报告我的想法
fail if you're making use of JDK
如果您使用的是JDK，将失败
internally api's so this is very very
内部api，所以这非常非常
useful so I'm going to show a couple of
有用，所以我将展示几个
examples and I'm just I've taken four
例子，我只是拿了四个
first start one of the the GlassFish jar
首先启动一个GlassFish罐子
files and just to show what the sample
文件，只是为了展示示例
output is when you run J tips - JDK
输出是当您运行J技巧时-JDK
internals what you're seeing here is a
内部结构您在这里看到的是
printout of a number of Sun dot security
打印一些Sun dot security
that's something ap eyes that are being
那是被眼睛所吸引的东西
directly referenced by code in this
在此直接由代码引用
security jar file I think what's
安全罐文件，我想是什么
happened here is is that there's an
发生在这里的是，有一个
internal framework within the within the
内部框架
security security library code that that
安全性安全库代码
is being used used here what's happening
正在使用这里发生了什么
is is pointing out that scum son
指出那败类的儿子
Enterprise comm IOP security something
企业通信IOP安全性
something something is making as a
做某事
direct reference to Sun security util
直接参考Sun Security util
object identifier this is possibly an
对象标识符，可能是
extreme case this is possibly being used
极端的情况下可能正在使用
for for convenient use but it gives you
为了方便使用，但它给您
an idea of what the JDK internalise
关于JDK内部化的想法
output produces the other thing at the
输出会在
end is is is that JJ tips has a little
最终是，JJ提示有一点
mapping of old historical internal api's
旧的历史内部api的映射
to new supported internal API so in this
到新的受支持的内部API，因此在此
case if you'll read down at the bottom
如果你从头开始读的话
of the slide it suggests changing your
幻灯片，它建议您更改
references to some security X 500 X 500
引用某些安全性X 500 X 500
named to Java security off X 500 X 500
授予Java安全性X 500 X 500
principal because that is a supported
主体，因为这是受支持的
API anyway the main thing is this is
无论如何，API最主要的是
this very very quick youmu jdk age to be
这个非常快的youmu jdk年龄是
able to just run this tool and see
能够仅运行此工具并查看
whether you have any dependencies on
您是否有任何依赖
internal API s so now that we know that
内部API，因此我们现在知道
this just this just this glassware jar
这只是这个玻璃器皿
file has is making use of internal API
文件已在使用内部API
so what happens if I were to run that
所以如果我跑那个会怎样
code with JDK 9 we will see
JDK 9的代码，我们将看到
it actually fails at wrong time with an
它实际上在错误的时间失败，并带有
illegal access error ignore the detail
非法访问错误忽略细节
of the error it's essentially saying
错误的本质上是说
that some code in this console on
在这个控制台上的一些代码
enterprise security something-something
企业安全性
is trying to access some security
正在尝试访问一些安全性
provider policy file in module Java base
Java基础模块中的提供者策略文件
ignore that we talked about Java base
忽略我们谈到的Java基础
later on in the later talks and then you
以后在以后的谈话中，然后你
see stack trace and it's essentially
查看堆栈跟踪，它本质上是
telling you it's it's it's it's it's a
告诉你这是它是这是一个
warning maybe it's fatal
警告也许是致命的
with glass this year that you're trying
今年你要用玻璃杯
to make use of internally api's I said
利用内部API的我说
earlier on that you would have got a
早些时候，你会得到一个
compilation error with JT case from JDK
来自JDK的JT案例的编译错误
6 an words if you try to make direct use
如果您尝试直接使用6个字
of internal API s now you've got the
内部API的数量，现在您有了
runtime enforcement and with this
运行时执行以及与此
stronger enforcement at compile time to
在编译时加强执行
this gives you an idea of the
这使您对
implications of strong capsulation and
强大的封装和
encapsulation of the JDK internal API s
JDK内部API的封装
now let's look another of an another
现在让我们来看看另一个
example I'm using a slightly older
例如，我使用的是稍旧的
version of Gradle 2 for those that are
Gradle 2的版本
tracking Gradle and I try to run the
跟踪Gradle，我尝试运行
kemal compiled Java task I've
我已经凯末尔编译的Java任务
highlighted in red that this is failing
以红色突出显示这是失败的
could not create an instance of calm
无法创造平静的实例
some tools Java C API
一些工具Java C API
Java C tool that's it not not a huge
Java C工具不是很大
amount of information there but Gradle
有大量的信息，但Gradle
is actually quite good in that you can
实际上是非常好的，因为你可以
you can give it a stack trace option on
你可以给它一个堆栈跟踪选项
the grader command to give you more
平地机命令为您提供更多
information so getting a failure here
信息，所以在这里失败
and if we run with the stack trace
如果我们使用堆栈跟踪
option we get a little bit more
选项，我们会得到更多
information we get a stack trace in this
我们在此获得堆栈跟踪的信息
case it's a legal access exception if
如果是合法访问例外
you if you know your X if you know your
你如果知道你的X如果你知道你的X
errors and exceptions in the Java
Java中的错误和异常
platform you know that the static
平台你知道静态
reference failing with an error
参考因错误而失败
equivalent work or reflection is is an
等效的工作或反思是
exception because core reflection does
异常，因为核心反射确实
the same access checks as as the virtual
与虚拟访问权限相同
machine so here we have some core
机器，所以在这里我们有一些核心
reflection usage in in in this older
在这个较旧的版本中使用反射
version of Gradle that's trying to make
试图制作的Gradle版本
use of an unsupported API in the Java C
在Java C中使用不受支持的API
compiler it's failing at at runtime so I
编译器在运行时失败，所以我
realize when you see these for the first
意识到当你第一次看到这些
time is these scary exceptions
时间是这些可怕的例外
just look scary but you don't panic I
只是看起来吓人，但你不要惊慌
said earlier on about about the result
之前关于结果说
was going to be a workaround and that
这将是一个解决方法，并且
workaround is we start with the command
解决方法是从命令开始
line version of it so for the four going
的线版本，所以四个
back to the GlassFish example I can get
回到GlassFish示例，我可以得到
the existing version of GlassFish to
GlassFish的现有版本
still run by giving it a bunch of
通过给它一堆仍然运行
command line options that tell us that I
告诉我们我的命令行选项
want to break encapsulation and really
想打破封装，真的
really get at these api's so out of the
真的可以使用这些api
box I cannot I cannot compile I can't
框，我不能，我不能编译，我不能
run and make use of these internal api's
运行并利用这些内部api
and but I can still get existing code to
而且我仍然可以获取现有代码
work via this command line option I'll
通过此命令行选项工作
explain the details of what this means
解释这意味着什么的细节
in a few minutes now I don't like to
几分钟后，我不喜欢
pick on on things beginning with G and
选择以G和
in the case of GlassFish there was
就GlassFish而言，
actually an issue that's already really
其实已经是一个真正的问题
tracking this issue so that this old
跟踪此问题，以便此旧
code that's using some but security
使用一些但安全的代码
classes will assume get fixed in time so
上课时间会固定，所以
back to the option that I just showed a
回到我刚刚显示的选项
few minutes ago and the format of this
几分钟前的格式
option and so then the name of the
选项，然后是名称
option is - - ad exports so one of the
选项是--广告导出，因此
other things and you may see this in
其他事情，您可能会在
some of the other presentations today or
今天的其他一些演讲或
this week is is we've started to and add
这周是我们开始添加
new command line options in JDK 9 that
JDK 9中的新命令行选项
are the new style in quotes so they're a
是引号中的新样式，因此它们是
bit more verbose in the UNIX style and
UNIX风格更加冗长，
the sort of uniquely JDK style options
独特的JDK样式选项
that we've had in the past so in this
我们过去曾经有过
case it's - - a - exports because and
如果是--a-出口是因为和
all of the new options by the way are
顺便说一下，所有新选项都是
are in this style the value to this
这种风格的价值
option is is as has three parts to it
选项是因为它包括三个部分
the source module package and then what
源模块包，然后是什么
the target module is if you come along
目标模块是您是否愿意
to the to the talks later today about
今天晚些时候的谈判
modules you can show how we've migrated
您可以展示我们如何迁移的模块
what was the monolithic platform into a
什么是整体平台
nice graph of modules the core module in
核心模块所在的模块的漂亮图表
the system is called Java base and
该系统称为Java基础，
that's what this one I'm specifying here
这就是我在这里指定的
is the name of the module then the
是模块的名称，然后
package name of the internal API that is
内部API的软件包名称，即
being used and then Who am I going to
被使用，然后我要去谁
give access to ignore the detail of what
允许忽略什么细节
all named is
全部命名为
if you attend the modularity talks that
如果您参加模块化讲座，
we're going to be doing today and
我们今天要去做
tomorrow and Wednesday then we'll
明天和星期三，我们将
explain a bit more about what what this
多解释一下这是什么
means in fact Alex is under the hood
意味着实际上亚历克斯在幕后
talk and goes through a lot about what
谈论并经历很多事情
this notion of unnamed module for now
目前未命名模块的概念
just assume it means the class path in
只是假设它意味着类路径在
other words I'm giving I'm exporting the
换句话说，我给我出口
Sun security provider package so that
Sun安全提供程序包，以便
can be used by code on the class path
可以被类路径上的代码使用
that's a simple way to to read this
这是阅读此书的简单方法
discuss command line we also in our
讨论命令行，我们也在
early access Bills have a way to do this
抢先体验法案有办法做到这一点
via the main application and manifest so
通过主应用程序和清单
in the in the main application jar file
在主应用程序jar文件中
you can take responsibility for and
您可以负责和
making use of these internal api's by
利用这些内部api
declaring in the manifest that exactly
在清单中明确声明
like we had in the command-line option
就像我们在命令行选项中一样
so that's all I want to say for now
所以这就是我现在要说的
about encapsulating internal API so I
关于封装内部API，所以我
want to move on and try and get through
想继续前进并尝试度过难关
some of the other things are the big
其他一些事情很重要
changes in jdk 9 right so what I want to
在jdk 9中更改对吧，所以我想要
talk about the binary structure of the
说说二进制结构
JRE in the JDK when I mean the binary
我指的是JDK中的JRE中的JRE
structure I'm essentially mean it's
结构我基本上是说
layout on disk the fact that we have a
在磁盘上布局的事实是，我们有一个
bin directory
bin目录
RGH are tools that you are these are
RGH是您的工具，这些是
things that you would have seen in the
你会在中看到的东西
JDK and the JRE releases going back
JDK和JRE版本可以追溯到
several years we're finally getting
几年我们终于
around to looking at this layout on disk
看看磁盘上的这种布局
so this is actually disruptive change of
所以这实际上是
tools I'll talk a little bit about about
我将谈论的一些工具
that in the next covering of slides with
在下一张幻灯片中
many motivations for finally reexamining
最终重新审查的许多动机
these dis layouts on disk when we move
当我们移动时这些磁盘上的布局
to a modular runtime what's happening is
到模块化运行时，正在发生的是
is that we're going to completely blur
是我们将要完全模糊
the historical and distinction between
历史和区别
the JRE and the Gerry plus tools that we
JRE和Gerry以及我们提供的工具
call the JDK it marks keynote we saw he
称它为JDK，这是我们看到他的主题演讲
created a little runtime that only had
创建了一个只有
one module or a small number of modules
一个模块或少量模块
this is another runtime there is the the
这是另一个运行时
the existing are the long-standing and
现有的是长期存在的
runtime image layout does not lend
运行时映像布局不可用
itself to doing this kind of blinking a
自己来做这种眨眼
whole bunch of modules together
整个模块在一起
and producing your own one time image
并制作自己的一次性图像
other motivations are things like the
其他动机是像
zip format we've been using the zip
zip格式，我们一直在使用zip
format as the basis for jar for a long
格式长期作为jar的基础
long time it's not an efficient way to
长期以来，这不是一种有效的方法
store the platform classes it's we have
存储我们拥有的平台类
had so many different startup and other
有这么多不同的创业公司和其他
performance issues related to jar files
与jar文件相关的性能问题
in our TVR especially as the platform
在我们的TVR中，尤其是作为平台
has got bigger and bigger and bigger
越来越大
over the years and so it's finally after
多年来，所以终于
20 years time to revisit this old format
20年的时间重新审视这种旧格式
there's lots of interesting things we
我们有很多有趣的事情
can do around performance and when we
可以围绕性能而做
reexamine and this so all of these
重新检查，所以所有这些
changes we went into em in - jdk age 39
我们进入39岁以下年龄段的变化
back in late 2014 it's a disruptive
早在2014年末
change for tools so disruptive change
换工具如此具有破坏性的改变
for id's compilers and so on as part of
用于id的编译器等
this we've introduced a supported way
我们介绍了一种受支持的方式
for these tools to be able to access the
这些工具才能访问
contents of the image so this is the
图片的内容，所以这是
first time we've had a supporter way for
第一次我们有支持者
tools to be able access the class files
能够访问类文件的工具
and resources so this is useful so a lot
和资源，所以这很有用
of the tools have already migrated to
的工具已经迁移到
making use of this particularly in early
特别是在早期使用
access form there's still some tools
访问表单中仍有一些工具
that haven't haven't got there yet just
还没到那儿
looking at it the old historical format
看着它的旧历史格式
this is JDK 8 you can see there's
这是JDK 8，您可以看到
essentially two levels of directory at
本质上是两个级别的目录
the top level you've got the bin
顶层有垃圾箱
directory where you'll find tools like
您将在其中找到类似工具的目录
Java and Java C within that you've got a
Java和Java C在其中
runtime and there's also a Lib directory
运行时，还有一个Lib目录
we defined tools that you are in they're
我们定义了您所使用的工具
going down the level you will actually
下降到您将实际达到的水平
find another bin directory with copies
查找另一个带有副本的bin目录
of the same tools and a Lib directory
相同的工具和一个Lib目录
where you find you would have found our
您找到的地方会找到我们的
GTR and a bunch of other jar files in
GTR和其他一堆jar文件
there there's other jar files they all
那里还有其他的jar文件
have they all have history as to how
他们都有关于如何的历史吗
they came into into being if you if you
他们应运而生
start digging into the Lib directory you
开始挖掘您的Lib目录
will actually find a whole bunch of
实际上会发现一大堆
other interesting files that some of
其他一些有趣的文件
them are supported configuration like
它们是受支持的配置，例如
for example the security policy file
例如安全策略文件
there's other there's other
还有其他还有其他
configuration files in there you're not
您不在的配置文件
really supposed to change those because
真的应该改变那些，因为
if you do then the JDK won't start up or
如果您这样做，那么JDK将无法启动，或者
the misbehave and so
行为不端等等
on we've never been clear as to what
关于什么我们从来就不清楚
what's the what's the configuration
什么是什么配置
that's intended to be so be edited
打算如此编辑
versus versus versus configuration that
vs vs vs配置
shouldn't really be edited because it's
不应真正对其进行编辑，因为
going to break things so the new format
会破坏东西，所以新格式
that we have in JDK 9 again as I said
正如我所说，我们再次在JDK 9中拥有
since since one of the AE since late
自从一个AE以来
2014 removes that one level of directory
2014删除该目录的一级
it's very very simple we just think of
我们想到的非常非常简单
it as as a as a only three interesting
作为一个只有三个有趣的
directories in it the bin directory as
bin目录中的目录
before where you'll find the Java launch
在找到Java启动之前
or java java c RM ID all of the other
或java java c RM ID其他
interesting tools that you'll find in
您会在其中找到有趣的工具
there a kampf directory which is where
那里有一个kampf目录
all of the configuration that is
所有的配置
intended to be edited is moved into this
拟编辑的内容已移至此
this is where you'll find the security
在这里您可以找到安全性
file this is where you'll find the
文件，这是您在其中找到的
things like the properties to configure
诸如要配置的属性之类的东西
the management agent all of these things
所有这些东西的管理代理
that you want to be able to edit are in
您想要能够进行编辑的
the one place everything else is in the
一处其他地方都在
Lib directory in some format that
库目录的某种格式
possibly will change over time in the
可能会随着时间的流逝而变化
case of the class files and this is
类文件的情况，这是
within the JDK we've put them into a
在JDK中，我们将它们放入
completely lock to Mai's format that
完全锁定了Mai的格式
that will change over time but is very
会随着时间而改变，但是非常
very useful for the JDK in terms of and
对于JDK而言，在和
startup and other performance things
启动和其他性能方面的事情
that we want to go into so that's all
我们想要进入的就是全部
I'll say for now about the the runtime
我现在就说一下运行时
image this is primarily in implications
图片主要是暗示
for for tools rather than in most
用于工具而不是大多数
applications I mentioned about removing
我提到的有关删除的应用程序
some deprecated methods so these are six
一些不推荐使用的方法，所以这是六个
supported Java dot star methods that
支持的Java点星方法
we're actually removing you probably
我们实际上可能是在删除您
don't recognize these or most people
不认识这些人或大多数人
won't recognize him these have been
不会认出他这些是
removed since the first build of JDK 9
自JDK 9的首次构建以来已删除
and I'm not aware of any bug reports
而且我不知道任何错误报告
which suggests that there's not too many
这表明没有太多
people that are reusing these these have
重复使用这些的人有
been deprecated since since age and they
自从年龄就被弃用，他们
were flagged for removal so as part of
被标记为要删除，因此作为
modulized in the platform which we
在我们调制的平台中
talked about in the next talk a little
在接下来的演讲中谈到了一点
bit is these are the six that were most
这些是最多的六个
problematic and had to be removed in
有问题的，必须在
order to actually get to the nice module
为了真正进入漂亮的模块
graph that we show on the next talk
我们在下一个谈话中显示的图形
there's some extension mechanism have
有一些扩展机制
been removed and the standards override
已被删除且标准被覆盖
mechanism hardly ever used originally
最初很少使用的机制
intended for app servers that are
适用于以下应用服务器
replacing and upgrading some of the
更换和升级一些
components in the in the JDK and the
JDK和
extension mechanism again this this
扩展机制再次这个
hasn't been widely used it was very much
还没有被广泛使用
a mis feature and but essentially it was
一个错误的功能，但本质上是
a way that you could actually don't jar
一种您实际上不会震撼的方式
files into the runtime image and have
文件放入运行时映像并具有
them mean you have a bloomin visible at
他们表示您在
compile and run time so not to these are
编译和运行时不要这样
not too interesting the next one might
下一个可能不太有趣
be kind of interesting so I want to show
有点有趣，所以我想展示
you a jar file on the classpath in GSR
您在GSR中的类路径上找到一个jar文件
three or five jar assume this jar file
三个或五个jar假定此jar文件
has a couple of annotations in there in
在其中有几个注释
the package Java X dot annotation I
包Java X点注释I
guess any one that most people may even
猜猜大多数人甚至可能
recognize these not nullable off off off
认识到这些不是不可为空的
off often used for defect detection in
常用于缺陷检测
applications these annotations are in
这些注释在应用程序中
the same package as the so-called common
与所谓的普通包装相同
annotations the GS are 250 GS or 250th
注释GS为250 GS或250th
and defined annotations so now what you
和定义的注释，所以现在你
have is by putting this jsr 305 on the
通过将jsr 305放在
class path I've got some annotations in
类路径中有一些注释
Java X annotation that are part of this
属于其中的Java X批注
other one API and they're loaded at
另外一个API，它们在以下位置加载
runtime by what's called the platform or
通过所谓的平台或
in the past the extension class loader
过去扩展类加载器
and then I've got the these these other
然后我得到这些其他
non notable nullable and so on on the
非显着可为空等
class path that are loaded by the
类加载的类路径
application class loader this is a
应用程序类加载器，这是一个
little bit strange what I've got here is
有点奇怪，我在这里得到的是
a split package problem I've got some
拆分包装问题，我有一些
some classes are part of the platform
一些类是平台的一部分
some are on the class path this is just
有些在课堂上，这只是
one of a couple of api's that are highly
高度可靠的api之一
problematic and the transaction api is
有问题的交易API
another one Java C defines a small
另一个Java C定义了一个小
subset of the transaction API the reason
交易API的子集的原因
it does that is is is part of supporting
它确实是支持的一部分
transactions with with with korba Java
与korba Java进行的交易
EE
电子工程
defines the full transaction API another
定义另一个完整的交易API
potential split package problem things
潜在的拆分包装问题
really go downhill when you start
当你开始真的走下坡路
looking at corba the core vendors the
看着corba的核心厂商
app servers typically will upgrade and
应用服务器通常会升级并
overlay a bunch of support for
叠加了对
additional and OMG standards so what has
其他和OMG标准
been proposed and what has been in JDK 9
已提出，JDK 9中的内容
for some time is that the modules that
一段时间以来，这些模块
are shared with Java EE and by the way
与Java EE共享
everything here all of these problematic
所有这里所有这些有问题的
packages they're all things that are
包就是一切
typically upgraded by Java EE they are
通常是通过Java EE升级的
not resolved by default now we haven't
默认情况下没有解决，我们还没有
talked about modules and resolution or
谈论模块和分辨率或
anything for now just when I say these
我刚才讲这些时的一切
modules are not resolved just just
模块不只是解决
assume that the types in the transaction
假设交易中的类型
API in any of these other six that I've
我所拥有的其他六个API中的任何一个
listed here they're not visible by
在这里列出，它们不可见
default
默认
it will appear as if those types do not
看起来好像那些类型没有
exist you get a go class that founder if
存在，你会得到一个创始人创建的
you try to run code that makes use of
您尝试运行利用以下代码
them we have documented in jet 260 a
我们已经在喷气飞机260 a中记录了它们
write up as to the rationale for this
写出这样做的理由
I'll read it out number one to avoid
我会读一号以避免
unnecessary conflicts of popular
不必要的流行冲突
libraries that define types in some of
在某些类型中定义类型的库
the same package like we saw in the
就像我们在
previous slides and number two to make
上一张幻灯片和第二张
it easier for existing application
现有应用程序更容易
servers to migrate to JDK 9 application
服务器迁移到JDK 9应用程序
servers often override the content of
服务器通常会覆盖
one or more of these modules and in the
这些模块中的一个或多个
near term they most likely do so by
他们很可能在短期内这样做
continuing to place the necessary
继续放置必要的
non-modular jars on the class path so
类路径上的非模块化jar
this is if you're using any of these and
这是如果您正在使用其中任何一个
there's six of them here and you don't
这里有六个，而你没有
know the module names because we haven't
知道模块名称，因为我们还没有
showed them yet when we will in the
向他们展示了我们何时会
other talks is we have organized these
其他讲座是我们组织了这些
these modules that are overlapping with
这些与之重叠的模块
with Java EE into six modules Java core
将Java EE分为六个模块Java核心
which you have a transaction Java
您有交易Java
annotations common job activation Java X
批注常用作业激活Java X
is our java xml ws for the web services
是我们用于Web服务的java xml ws
in java xml bind for the for the binding
在java xml bind中进行绑定
api's again we don't panic here because
api再次让我们在这里不惊慌，因为
we're always thinking through and what
我们一直在思考，什么
options you have to keep the existing
您必须保留现有选项
world going
世界走向
it's very simple on the command line if
在命令行上，如果
I'm using CORBA and I can continue it
我正在使用CORBA，我可以继续
will continue to work exactly as it did
将继续像以前一样工作
in JDK 9 by just using this option
在JDK 9中，只需使用此选项
called add module add modules Alex just
称为添加模块添加模块Alex只是
pointed out that I've a typo here this
指出我这里有错字
is this should be plural modules so add
这应该是多个模块，所以添加
modules Java corba what that does is it
Java Corba模块的作用是什么
essentially adds that module to the set
本质上将该模块添加到集合中
of modules that should be resolved as
应解决的模块数量
start of existing code that uses coral
使用珊瑚的现有代码的开始
will continue to work with this option
将继续使用此选项
for the App servers not really the most
对于App服务器来说并不是最
applications it's possible to deploy an
应用程序，可以部署
upgraded version of CORBA as a module
CORBA的升级版作为模块
and you just use this upgrade module
而您只使用此升级模块
path this is like the the module
这就像模块的路径
equivalent of the endorsed override
等同于认可的替代
mechanism that is that I mentioned
我提到的机制
earlier on mostly only interesting to
早些时候只对
the app servers it's also possible
应用服务器，这也是可能的
because there are because the these
因为有这些
modules are not resolved by default I
默认情况下，模块不解析
can actually just throw this on the
实际上可以把它扔在
classpath there's no split package
classpath没有拆分包
issues so there's a couple of possible
问题，所以有两种可能
workarounds for this this type of issue
此类问题的解决方法
if you're making direct use of these
如果您直接使用这些
api's one final thing just to say on
api的最后一句话就是说
this is this policy of not resolving the
这是不解决的政策
e modules by default is very much
e模块默认情况下非常
something that we're dependent on
我们所依赖的东西
feedback on so we need to see over the
的反馈，因此我们需要查看
next couple of months and whether you're
接下来的几个月，以及您是否
whether this type of a changes is
这种变化是否
disruptive or not maybe this set of
是否具有破坏性
modules should be just we will actually
模块应该只是我们将实际上
see this is being in JDK 9 for quite
看到这是在JDK 9
some time there's been very very little
有一段时间很少
feedback on us what it's possible that
反馈给我们的可能性
not too many people making use of these
没有太多人利用这些
api's or trying things out okay a couple
api或尝试一些可以的方法
of other things are interested in
其他事物感兴趣
changes in JDK 9 I'm not going to spend
我不会花在JDK 9中的更改
time on them today is is the application
今天是他们的时间是应用程序
the extension class loader which is
扩展类加载器
renamed the platform class loader are no
重命名为平台类加载器否
longer instances of URL class loader
URL类加载器的更长实例
we've had a couple of cases where
我们有几个案例
there's existing library code have been
现有的库代码已经
making the assumption that the
假设
application class loader is an instance
应用程序类加载器是一个实例
of this type and blindly casts to that
这种类型，盲目地投掷到
type and then of course because this is
类型，然后当然是因为
completely changed in JDK 9 they get a
在JDK 9中完全改变，他们得到了
class castex
Castex类
action more details on our routine
在我们的日常活动中采取更多细节
object 261 on that there's a couple of
对象261上有几个
options are being removed like the
选项被删除，如
ability to override or prepend to the
超越或前置于
blue class path the reason is is the
蓝班路径的原因是
blue class path as we know it really
我们真正知道的蓝色阶级之路
doesn't exist in JDK 9 and it's all part
在JDK 9中不存在，并且全部
of moving moving to modules and the
转移到模块和
system properties associated with that
与之相关的系统属性
have been removed as well I want to
我也想被删除
quickly go through a couple of other
很快经历另外两个
things and the version skeet stream chip
事物和版本双向双向码流芯片
223 surprisingly this is probably the
223令人惊讶的是，这可能是
most disruptive change that we've have
我们拥有的最具破坏性的变化
had in JDK nine so far and the JDK 9
到目前为止，JDK 9和JDK 9
versioning scheme has historically been
历史上，版本控制方案是
confusing because I read from the gyp
令人困惑，因为我从吉卜赛读过
this is again and the chip in its
这又是它的芯片
motivations has a little write-up which
动机有一些写作
release contains all of the most recent
版本包含所有最新的
security fixes is a JDK 7 update 55 our
安全修复程序是JDK 7更新55
JDK 7 update 60 it looks like JDK 7
JDK 7更新60看起来像JDK 7
update 60 is 5 releases later than
更新60比5晚发行
update 55 so therefore it must include
更新55，因此它必须包括
more security fixes that compute that
更多的安全修复程序可以计算出
that conclusion is incorrect these two
结论是错误的，这两个
releases contain exactly the same
版本包含完全相同
security releases security fixes
安全发布安全修复程序
security releases based on the previous
基于先前版本的安全版本
minor version are odd numbers
次要版本是奇数
incremented by 5 r by 6 if necessary in
在必要时将5 r增加6
order to keep the update number odd
为了使更新数量保持奇数
always being confusing this is the
总是令人困惑，这是
proposed new version string format
建议的新版本字符串格式
you'll find all the details in Jeff to
您将在Jeff中找到所有详细信息，以
2023 the simple way to summarize this
2023年总结的简单方法
slide is after 20 years
幻灯片是20年后
we're finally dropping the leading one
我们终于放弃了领先者
changing the version and scheme has an
更改版本和方案有一个
impact on system properties and this is
对系统属性的影响，这是
where it's been quite a disruptive
在相当破坏性的地方
change there's a lot of code out there
更改那里有很多代码
that reads the Javadoc version property
读取Javadoc版本属性
and parses it and so this one thing just
并解析它，所以这件事只是
to keep in mind if you have any code
要记住是否有任何代码
that is dependent on the version see
取决于版本，请参见
what I haven't gone through today in the
我今天没有经历过的
in this slide is visit there's a new API
在此幻灯片中，有一个新的API
prefer for Java C 9 and it's called
更喜欢Java C 9，它被称为
runtime dot version you can actually
您实际上可以运行的点版本
call one time that version and returns
调用一次该版本并返回
you a version object that M allows you
您使用的M版本对象
to introspect the major minor and other
反思主要未成年人和其他
things about the about the version
关于版本的事情
number very very useful so I've been
数字非常非常有用，所以我一直
talking about disruptive things I just
谈论我只是破坏性的事情
want to spend a few minutes on things on
想花一些时间在
an honor to features that I think are
我认为很荣幸的功能
interesting and when you start looking
有趣，当你开始寻找
at at migration from 8 to 9 and these
从8迁移到9
are the DS are described in 238 and 247
DS在238和247中有描述
238 is multi release jars 248 is
238是多重释放罐子248是
compiled for older platform versions so
针对较旧的平台版本进行了编译，因此
because so consider this scenario I'm
因为考虑这种情况我
making use of internal api's but there's
利用内部api，但是
a supported API available in java c 9 so
Java c 9中提供了受支持的API，因此
maybe maybe you're making use of our
也许您正在利用我们的
handles so you don't have to make use of
处理，所以您不必利用
some of the lower-level api's may be
一些较低级别的api可能是
using making use of the the old internal
利用旧的内部
XML API is for serializer or catalog and
XML API用于序列化程序或目录，
and there's a new catalog API and 9 my
还有一个新的目录API和9
application well I really wanted to work
应用程序很好，我真的很想工作
on a time when you need to build it on
在需要将其构建时
ease and then run on age or 9 so this is
放松，然后在9岁或9岁时跑步，这是
a common scenario particularly
常见的情况，特别是
particularly when you're we're talking
特别是当你在谈论
about 2016 and JDK 9 is and isn't isn't
关于2016年和JDK 9是不是
going to be released into 2017 so I need
即将发布到2017年，所以我需要
to be able to do this kind of scenario
能够做到这种情况
so one feature in JDK 9 and
因此，JDK 9和
is multi release jars the jar format has
是多版本jar，jar格式有
been extended to allow multiple job
扩展以允许多个工作
release specific class files to coexist
发布特定的类文件以共存
in the same archive I'm not going to
在同一档案中，我不会
spend a huge amount of time on the
花大量时间在
bullets today but it's something to look
今天的子弹，但它看起来
up and it's very very useful feature so
，这是非常非常有用的功能
if a multi release jar file has in its
如果一个多发行版jar文件中包含
in its manifest a natural beaut named
在其表现形式中，自然美人
multi - release that has a value true so
多次发布，其值为true
it's a boolean and then has a section
这是一个布尔值，然后有一个部分
meta INF version / than the version
meta INF版本/比版本
number in this case nine and the classes
在这种情况下，数字是九
and the resources in that section can
并且该部分中的资源可以
override what's in the top level or base
覆盖顶层或底层的内容
section so if we were to study this
因此，如果我们要研究这个
example we can see that we've got there
例如，我们可以看到我们已经到了那里
to help produc classes in this jar file
帮助生产这个jar文件中的类
in the top section we've got comic
在顶部，我们有漫画
neistat's internal helper class and down
neistat的内部帮手课程
in the meta-inf versions nine
在meta-inf版本9中
there's also another calm acne stats
还有一个平静的痤疮统计数据
internal helper class when you run
运行时的内部帮助程序类
online the bottom one will be used when
在线底部的将在以下情况下使用
you run an eight the one in the top
你在顶部跑了一个八
level our base section will be used so
我们的基础部分将被使用
in this example and I'll run it just as
在这个例子中，我将像
the main application jar for the moment
目前主要的应用程序罐
when I run at an eight we can see that
当我八点跑步时，我们可以看到
calm acne stats internal helper loaded
镇静痤疮统计信息内部助手已加载
from the top section our base section
从顶部开始我们的基础部分
online is loaded from the meta-inf serve
在线从meta-inf服务加载
INF versions this is very very useful
INF版本，这非常有用
when you're trying to do this migration
当您尝试进行此迁移时
from internal api's to and supportive
从内部api到支持
api's immediately when you start
api刚开始时
thinking about oh now i've got to have
想着哦，现在我必须要
jdk age and the jdk nine in my build
jdk年龄和我构建中的jdk九
environment in order to do this I want
为了做到这一点我想要的环境
to make aware of one other one other
互相认识
change our third feature in jdk 9 which
更改我们在jdk 9中的第三个功能
is the ability to confer the compiler to
是赋予编译器以
target old releases we've always been
针对我们一直以来的旧版本
able to do java c - sourced at target
能够做Java C-源于目标
seven or eight and then give it a boot
七个或八个然后启动
class path
课堂路径
okay that means I have to have another
好的，那意味着我必须再有一个
JDK on my system if I'm on eight I'm
我的系统上有JDK（如果我八岁）
going to target seven then I have that
要瞄准七个目标
mom I'm going to Jade gate for building
妈妈我要去玉门大厦
I'm targeting seven in order to be
我的目标是七个
ensured that the compilation is
确保编译是
consistent I can do that all now at one
我可以一口气做到这一点
step in in JDK 9 I can do Java C - -
在JDK 9中可以使用Java C--
release whatever my target release is
释放我的目标版本
and it's equivalent to their source -
相当于他们的来源-
targets that new class path with only
仅以该新类路径为目标
having one JDK on the system so this is
系统上只有一个JDK，所以这是
really really nice with JDK 9 in my
我的JDK 9真的很棒
built environment I can compile to six
我可以编译为六个的构建环境
seven eight or nine without having
七八九而无
multiple J decays on my system so that
我系统上的多个J衰变
compiled multi release jars provides a
编译的多版本jar提供了
great way for actually moving away from
远离现实的好方法
internal api's and building applications
内部api和构建应用程序
that run on different versions of the
在不同版本的
platform believe there is a talk
平台相信有一个话题
tomorrow on maven - that will touch on
明天在Maven上-这将继续
on some of the support for for these
对这些的一些支持
features so I wanted to start wrapping
功能，所以我想开始包装
up and so a couple of things to start
起，所以有几件事要开始
thinking about move for for jdk 9 the
考虑为jdk 9移动
most important thing that I've that I've
我拥有的最重要的东西
shown in this slide deck today is the J
今天在这张幻灯片中显示的是J
tips tool very few people put up their
提示工具很少有人提出
hands when I polled the audience earlier
当我较早地对观众进行投票时
on so there's there's not a huge
所以那里没有很大
awareness of this of this tool to do a
意识到这个工具要做一个
static analysis on your libraries and
对您的库进行静态分析
applications it's a really really good
应用程序真的非常好
tool to quickly identify whether you're
快速识别您是否正在使用的工具
using and any JDK internal API s so
使用和任何JDK内部API一样
that's one thing to to be aware of the
这是要注意的一件事
version change as I said has been highly
正如我所说，版本变更非常重要
disruptive a lot of open source code has
破坏性很多开源代码都有
been catching up and over over the last
在过去一直在追赶
six to nine months I have no doubt
六个月至九个月我毫无疑问
there's a huge amount of other code out
还有大量其他代码
there in applications that's parsing the
在应用程序中解析
value of Java dot version and isn't
Java点版本的值，不是
going to get the right answer with nine
九点就能得到正确答案
so that's something to check out
所以这是要检查的东西
primarily for tools but maybe you've got
主要用于工具，但也许您已经
this already is this is that we've had a
这已经是我们已经有一个
lot of code that has assumed there's an
许多代码假设
RTR it starts looking for jar files in
RTR它开始在以下位置查找jar文件
the JDK Lib directory or Jerry Lib
JDK Lib目录或Jerry Lib
directory because it needs to find
目录，因为它需要查找
miles this is all change as I said
就像我说的，一切都改变了
because it's a new layout in JDK 9 what
因为这是JDK 9中的新布局
are things to be aware of is is some
要注意的是一些
people did put up their hands at the
人们确实举起了手
beginning is there are weekly JDK 9
开始有每周JDK 9
early access bills so that and we're
提早使用账单，以便我们
working on modules we also do a jigsaw
在模块上工作，我们也做拼图
early access builds on a regular basis
定期进行早期访问
as well there's always early access
而且总是很早就可以进入
bills to download and try out I pointed
账单下载并尝试一下，我指出
out a couple of the things that help
列出了一些有帮助的东西
with the migration the multi release
随着迁移的多版本
jars and compiling to old versions
罐子并编译到旧版本
that's also worth checking out more
这也值得一试
information so we're working on the
信息，所以我们正在努力
module system and the module and and the
模块系统，模块和
modular JDK for JT t 9 this is all being
适用于JT t 9的模块化JDK
done in open JDK under project jigsaw
在项目Jigsaw下的开放JDK中完成
there's the links to the project page
有到项目页面的链接
and the mailing list early access bills
和邮件列表抢先体验账单
for JDK 9 or early access downloads is
对于JDK 9或抢先体验下载是
there the Jade EPS tool has its own wiki
那里的Jade EPS工具有自己的Wiki
page that Amanda Chung has been
钟欣欣（Amanda Chung）
maintaining that is a useful page to be
维护那是一个有用的页面
able to see a quick list of internal API
能够查看内部API的快速列表
is versus supported ap is that would be
是与支持的ap是
better API ste to use I've also included
使用的更好的API ste也包括在内
some links to and the JYP's that I
与我的JYP的一些链接
talked about towards the end of this EM
谈到即将结束的EM
session I'll come back to this slide in
会议，我将回到本幻灯片
a few minutes but just just advertise
几分钟，但只是做广告
the other sessions that we're actually
我们实际上正在参加的其他会议
doing here I said this is the first of
我在这里说这是第一个
five sessions that we're doing Alex and
我们正在做五个会议，Alex和
I are back in no sir
我没有先生了
I'm back here 2:30 about introduction to
我回到这里2:30关于介绍
modules the two of us are back here
我们两个人回到这里
later in the afternoon to do advanced
下午晚些时候做高级
Alex then has project under sorry the
亚历克斯然后有项目在对不起
services and projects under the hood
引擎盖下的服务和项目
tomorrow and then we have repeats for
明天，然后我们重复
the sessions are actually repeated we
这些会议实际上是重复的
also have a hack session on Wednesday
在星期三也有黑客会议
first thing in the morning and I think
早上第一件事，我想
they're all mostly even this room or
他们几乎全都是这个房间
next door
隔壁
so back to the links and I think we're
回到链接，我认为我们
done we've only got a few minutes for
完成，我们只有几分钟的时间
questions but if you want to ask some
问题，但如果你想问一些
questions please go ahead we may have to
问题，请继续，我们可能不得不
take some of the questions outside after
之后带一些外面的问题
if we run out of time
如果我们没时间了
you have to shout
你必须大喊
okay I didn't quite catch all of the
好吧，我没有完全抓住所有
question but I think what you said is
问题，但我认为你说的是
this is that there some some libraries
这是一些图书馆
are having problems with nine because
有九个问题，因为
they're using internally api's okay so
他们正在内部使用api，所以
and all I can say is until they migrate
我只能说直到他们迁移
away from those API s we have some ways
远离那些API，我们有一些方法
to mitigate it via the command line
通过命令行减轻它
options that I showed that that that's
我表明的选择是
really our our solution for that at the
真的，我们在
moment
时刻
right so the question is is with multi
对，所以问题在于
release jars does it imply multiple
释放罐是否暗示多个
source trees I think and I think that's
我认为是源代码树
a that's that's that that's a really
那就是那真的
good question so the the multi release
好问题，所以多发行
jar feature doesn't prescribe a source
jar功能未规定来源
layout for for that what you would have
您将拥有的布局
to have some way to be able to support
有某种方式可以支持
that sorry Robert is this something
抱歉罗伯特是这个东西
you're going to talk about okay you're
你要谈论好吧
sitting actually beside Robert Schulte
坐在罗伯特·舒尔特旁边
whose leads maven and people give me
他们的线索专家和人们给我的
giving a talk tomorrow and I think we'll
明天演讲，我想我们会
cover this everyone is prepared that's
掩盖这个，每个人都准备好了
great okay okay thank you
很好，很好，谢谢